and she said, okay, what you need
to do is you need to tell a story.
Tell me a story. And I thought
this was a really interesting
way of explaining it, rather than
kind of fretting about
language selection and
all this kind of stuff.
Tell me a story. Because
what I realised is we can all
tell stories. So we tell stories
to our mates down the pub.
We tell like our partners, stories
about what happened at work.
When we were teenagers, we
told our parents stories,
like when we got into trouble.
Kind of like if the police
find a body under our patio,
we have to tell some
kind of story, right?
So there's lots and lots of
stories and we know how to tell
those stories. We know how to
kind of pick that language.
And so what I sort of realised about,
even if it's non-fiction, it's the same,
is you have to come up with a way
of telling the story
about whatever it is that
you're writing.